{
    "subject": "resource/Robert_Lowry_(writer)",
    "predicate": "ontology/deathDate",
    "object": "1994",
    "human_readable": "Robert Lowry (writer) died in 1994.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8876137733459473,
            "question": "Was Robert Lowry a writer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8378424048423767,
            "question": "When did Robert Lowry die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7588164210319519,
            "question": "In what decade did Robert Lowry die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6395465135574341,
            "question": "What year was Robert Lowry born in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.63529372215271,
            "question": "What was the cause of Robert Lowry's death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5811693072319031,
            "question": "What is Robert Lowry known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43263593316078186,
            "question": "What was Robert Lowry's legacy in the literary world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41195887327194214,
            "question": "Who were some of Robert Lowry's influences?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3928079903125763,
            "question": "What were some of Robert Lowry's works?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3188721835613251,
            "question": "Where did Robert Lowry live and work?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Robert Lowry (writer) died in 1994.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3751_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What were some of Robert Lowry's works?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3751_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who were some of Robert Lowry's influences?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3751_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was Robert Lowry's legacy in the literary world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3751_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3751_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3751_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3751_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3751_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3751_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3751_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3751_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3751_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3751_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3751_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I can confirm that:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`\n\nThe triple \"Robert Lowry (writer) died in 1994\" is supported by the documents. Specifically, document `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3751/re-ranker-msmarco/78.txt` states that Robert Lowry was born on March 28, 1919 and died on December 5, 1994 in Cincinnati, Ohio, USA."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that Robert James Collas Lowry, the writer mentioned, died on December 5, 1994. This aligns with the statement \"Robert Lowry (writer) died in 1994.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Information from sources 1 and 4 state Robert Lowry (writer) was born in 1919 and died in 1994.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}